<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<testimonials>
	<item>
		<content>Searching for businesses, products and services over the Internet is much easier and quicker than leafing through the Yellow Pages, for example. Every time a potential or an existing client wants to find out more about your business, they can easily do so, especially if you have added a "FAQ" section. Your customers can always keep in touch with you and your business, all they need to know is your website’s address.</content>
		
	</item>
	<item>
		<content>Your business profile will be accessible from EVERYWHERE. No other ad medium provides such global coverage. You will not depend on restricted phone book entry presentations any more. What is more important, more and more customers are nowadays referring to the Internet when searching for products, services and businesses.</content>
	
	</item>
	<item>
		<content>People will not buy your products or services unless they know that they actually exist. You can tell your potential audience much more through a WEBSITE than you could possibly do via any print advertisements, Yellow Pages listings, or TV/radio commercials. There are no limitations as far as space, time, nationality and residency are concerned. You can say as many things as you want, to as many people as you wish. And your business representation can be as resourceful as is the Internet itself.</content>
		
	</item>
	<item>
		<content>Your website practically runs NON-STOP PROMOTIONS of your business! Your customers will always be able to obtain thorough up-to-date information about your services or products. Instead of having to rely on randomly aired TV or radio commercials, they can simply browse through your website whenever they like.</content>
		
	</item>
	<item>
		<content>A website is available to you 24 hours a day, 7 days a week, 365 days a year. It will be your hardest working employee, never getting sick, or taking a holiday. And you can rest assured that your website is always there for you – to answer your customers’ questions, or to collect their feedback on your behalf.</content>
		
	</item>
	<item>
		<content>Prospective clients can learn about you and your business at any time of the day simply by visiting your website, so you won’t have to be present or involved with the process in any way. The time you would otherwise have spent on answering or re-directing your customers’ questions can be now saved and invested in other activities that can increase your profits and further enhance the scope of your business.</content>
		
	</item>
	<item>
		<content>You can save a lot of money you would have otherwise spent on print ads, brochures, coupons, flyers, specials, newsletters or mailings. What’s more, updating the information on your website is always quick, easy and amazingly efficient, whereas regular renewals of printed materials can be quite expensive and time consuming. The fact is, nothing is more valued in any business than optimal productivity at minimum cost possible.</content>
		
	</item>
	
</testimonials>